talkcity.com 2002-12-26

# Home Pages at Talk City: Your Privacy In Our Community

  | 

The following outlines our policies for information gathering and dissemination. 

#### NOTICE: Policies for Individuals Under the Age of 13

[Talk City ](http://www.talkcity.com/)is intended for individuals age 13 and over only. We do not accept registrations from children under the age of 13, as we do not provide content for children. Parents please read the statement below for a complete explanation. 

__PARENTS PLEASE READ:__   
Due to the interactive nature of our site, and in order to comply with Federal laws designed to protect your children on the Internet, we do not permit children to register on our site. However, you can easily find a variety of places on the Web that are designed with the safety and best interests of your children in mind. We suggest that you do a search in one of the search engines under the words "kids sites." This should provide a vast selection of sites where your kids will be safely entertained - making the Internet a better place for everyone 

#### Member Registration:

Any visitor who wishes to chat, create a forum, own a chat room, build home pages, or use other free or premium (paid) services available on the Talk City site is asked to complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give information such as name, email address, birth date information, gender, country of residence and zip code if applicable. Certain services may additionally require that users provide postal mailing addresses, telephone numbers, or other information. Optional data fields such as marital status, household income, interest areas, etc. may be included. Talk City DOES NOT directly collect credit card or other financial information from users for premium/paid services. This information is collected by a trusted third-party such as PayPal, Inc. (www.paypal.com) and is not disclosed to Talk City or to Talk City marketing partners. 

We encourage our users to provide accurate and valid registration information so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. In addition, failure to provide a valid email address may inhibit our ability to notify you of critical service information, including the renewal of subscription services or changes in service or access to the Talk City web site. 

Users may need to register more than once for certain services offered by Talk City and/or its marketing partners and/or previously provided registration information may be used to "pre-populate" a registration form when a user registers for a new Talk City service. . 

#### Advertising 

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some member data is shared with the advertising companies. 

#### Third-Party Service Providers

Talk City partners with a variety of service providers to bring you services and enhanced features such as email. Information collected about members during registration may be shared with these partners in order to allow us to deliver the service in question. Links to these partner sites and their respective privacy policies are included below: 

  * [CP Software, Inc.](http://www.cpsoftware.com/)  ( [Privacy Policy](http://www.cpsoftware.com/privacy)) 

#### Special Offers Marketing

Talk City uses the information we collect during the registration process(s) to allow us to deliver promotional offers of interest to you. By submitting information during the registration process, you are allowing us to share this information with some or all of these partners so they can deliver special offers that may be of interest to you. In addition, these partners may use your information for direct marketing applications, including data enhancement. By submitting your information, you agree to the terms of their respective privacy policies. 

Links to these partner sites and their respective Privacy Policies is provided below. 

  * Virtumundo, Inc.

#### Links:

The Talk City web site also contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Talk City, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

#### Talk City Newsletters:

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletters, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. A user can unsubscribe from the email by writing to the following email address unsubscribe@myesp.com and requesting to be removed from the newsletter mail list. 

#### Surveys & Contests:

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see the choice/opt-out section below). 

#### Tell-A-Friend:

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Talk City will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Talk City, Inc stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Talk City, Inc via email at unsubscribe@corp.talkcity.com to request the removal of this information from the database. 

#### Public Forums:

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

#### Talk City Downloads:

From time to time, Talk City may include the automatic or mandatory download of new products, applets, etc. to the user's computer at the point of registration for various Talk City services. While Talk City reserves the right to include these downloads, their maintenance, and occasional upgrading, it will also provide users with the means to uninstall and/or remove these downloads at their discretion. . All downloaded products will include an "uninstall" feature or will be removable via the computer's "Add/Remove" program feature. Talk City reserves the right to change or amend its list of marketing partners at any time without notice. 

#### Cookies:

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user, such as nickname, age, zip code and gender. Talk City uses "cookies" to improve your experience on the site and to assist advertisers in providing you with advertisements targeted toward your interests. 

A user may elect to reject the cookie and still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to download or view movies, videos etc. on the Talk City Productions Video Player, nor will they be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. 

Talk City's cookie "lives" on your hard drive and allows you to log in to all services on our site without having to enter your password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, our ad companies collects cookies received with banner ads, and we do not have access to this information or control over these cookies. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. 

#### Log Files:

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

We also track the total number of visitors to our site in an aggregate form (this means you're one of the bunch, your information isn't singled out) to allow us to update and improve our site, and tell other people something about the numbers of people who come to talkcity.com. Personally identifiable information is not extracted in this process, unless necessary to identify, communicate and take appropriate action in incidents where a member is in violation of a Talk City Terms of Service or Code of Conduct policy. In such instances, this information is used only by Talk City management in the enforcing of such policies or by external law enforcement agencies as may be requested and/or required by law. 

#### Aggregate information:

We may also share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

#### Site and Service Updates:

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email. 

#### Correction/Updating Personal Information:

If any of the information you have provided us in the registration has changed you can make changes through MYINFO area on www.talkcity.com 

#### Terms of Service and Talk City Standards/Codes of Conduct

All services on Talk City include Terms of Service and Talk City Standards/Code of Conduct policies to which any participating member must agree to adhere by. Talk City reserves the right to monitor all activities undertake by its users while on the Talk City site, or while using any Talk City product or service, in order to ensure that these Terms of Service and Codes of Conduct are not violated. This includes the automatic logging and review of chat room text messaging, home page content, membership in Talk City Clubs, etc. In the event that a member violates a Talk City Terms of Service or Code of Conduct, Talk City reserves the right to revoke a user's Talk City Membership or use of any free or premium service. In the event that Talk City revokes a premium service for which the member has paid a subscription fee, such revocation of service may, at Talk City's sole discretion, be without refund. In the event that a Talk City member is suspected of being in violation with a Talk City Terms of Service or Code of Conduct policy, or with any law - local, state, federal, or otherwise - Talk City reserves the right to use, and share with any such law enforcement agency, any and all user data available to it to identify, and communicate with the member in violation and/or as needed in the revocation of its membership, rights to services, or in compliance with the request of any law enforcement agency. 

For a complete review of Talk City's Terms of Service and Code of Conduct policies, [click here ](http://www.talkcity.com/csa/)

#### Choice/Opt-Out:

You are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' ' of having your information used for purposes not directly related to our site. Opt-out/unsubscribe options are available to you at the point of registration and/or are included in the body of any email offer coming to you from Talk City. User's who select the 'opt out' feature of any promotion will have their email address removed Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, contact [privacy@myesp.com ](mailto:privacy@myesp.com)

#### Notification of Changes:

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to the privacy policy statement available on www.talkcity.com If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner by using an "opt-out/unsubscribe" feature included in the email or on the Talk City web site. Instructions for doing so will be provided. 

#### Security:

Talk City takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/subscription form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number ), that information is used and stored by entrusted third-party billing and payment clearing houses such as [PayPal](http://www.paypal.com/). 

If you have any questions about the security at our web site, you can send an email to: [privacy@myesp.com](mailto:privacy@myesp.com)

|    
---|---|---
